Wake up early in the morning, trying to figure out how to get my point across the many rivers of doubt.
Cause it's got us in a chokehold, a conundrum if you will.
I feel like I was called back to music because music is the most potent way to connect to folks.
For the people, we ain't going nowhere.
Our bodies make music, nature makes music.
Thus we're on a frequency that connects directly to music.
I also got tired of just talking like everybody else.
We know the way is to preserve the knowledge, the names, the words.
Almost bust my ass.
Ancestral transmissions, 4K visions of the end of empire when we vibrate higher, higher, higher, higher.